# **ALEN GEO**

# Full Stack Developer

Phone: 9074064070,

Email: calistusalan@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Birth Date: 02/10/1994 Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single Nationality: India

Address: Kandanam Parambil House, Marunnukada,

Palluruthy, Ernakulam, Kerala.

Self-Taught Full Stack Developer with one year of self-learning. Proficient in CSS with the ability to utilize Grid and Flexbox together to build smooth layouts. Rapid development of HTML using Emmet. Knowledge of deployment in GitHub. In progress of learning NodeJs by creating a website. Alumnus of Brototype, trained in Brocamp 2022.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Branch Manager - Reliance Industries Pvt Ltd

Ernakulam, Kerala March 2017 - May 2018

- Developing store strategies to raise customers' pool, expand store traffic and optimize profitability.
- Meeting sales goals by training, motivating, mentoring and providing feedback to store staff.
- Ensuring high levels of customer satisfaction through excellent service.

#### Branch Manager - MyG

Ernakulam, Kerala June 2018 - February 2019

- Developing store strategies to raise customers' pool, expand store traffic and optimize profitability.
- Meeting sales goals by training, motivating, mentoring and providing feedback to store staff.
- Ensuring high levels of customer satisfaction through excellent service.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sree Rama Varma - First School Leaving Certificate (FSLC) (Primary Education)

Ernakulam, Kerala. March 2011 - March 2012

Sree Rama Varma - Senior Secondary School Certificate (SSCE)

(Secondary Education)

Ernakulam, Kerala. March 2013 - March 2014

# TMC College - Diploma

(Hospitality & Tourism Management)

Rochor, Singapore. May 2019 - May 2021

# **SKILLS**

- Full Stack Developer
- Excellent Communication
- Time Management

## LANGUAGE

- Malayalam
- English
- Hindi

## **HOBBIES**

- Playing Guitar
- Watching Movies
- Internet Surfing